A Guide to the St. Mark's Episcopal Church Records, 1866-2016
Library of Virginia
- Property -- Painting, 1980-1983. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Property -- Painting Interior, not dated. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Property -- Parking Lot, 1969-1981. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Property -- Repair of Chancel Stained Glass Windows, 1955. (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Property -- Roof, 1980-1982. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Property -- Storm Windows, 1980-1981. (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Proposed Budgets, 1936-1955. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Publications -- "A Pattern for Life", 1965. (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Publications -- "Always a Priority", not dated. (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Publications -- Ceremony for Laying Corner-Stones, not dated. (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Racial Study Commission, 1960. (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Refugee Family, 1955-1959. (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Roll of Members, 1908. (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Scrapbook -- Miscellaneous Loose Pages (oversized), 1942-1947. (Box 48)
- Scrapbook -- St. Mark's Church, Dorcester, Massachusetts, 1944. (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Service of Dedication, The Robert Crossland Hyde Memorial Organ, 1965. (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Services -- Master Schedule, 1974-1977. (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Services -- Master Schedule, 1977-1978. (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Services -- Master Schedule, 1978-1980. (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Shut-Ins List, 1974-1977. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- St. Christina Chapter, 1972. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- "St. Mark's Beacon", 1926-1935. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- St. Mark's Episcopal Church: An Historical Prospective, not dated. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- St. Mark's Presents: Showtime, 1984. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- St. Mark's Stain Glass Windows research by Elizabeth Deane, 2016. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- St. Mary's Hospital, 1973. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- St. Paul's Church, Richmond, 1968. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- St. Peter's Church, Richmond, 1968. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- St. Philip's Church, Richmond, 1968. (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Statistical Information, 1975. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Statement and Budget, 1917. (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Sunday School, 1928. (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1970. (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1971. (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1972. (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1973. (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1974. (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1975. (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1976. (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Transfers from St. Mark's, 1977-1978. (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1970. (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1971. (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1972. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1973. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1974. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1975. (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1976. (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Transfers to St. Mark's, 1977-1978. (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Transfers to/from St. Mark's, 1963-1966. (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1935-1946. (Box 49)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1947-1958. (Box 50)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1959-1970. (Box 50)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1971-1979. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1979-1982. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Income and Disbursement Account Book, 1982-1985. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1933. (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1934. (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1935. (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1936. (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1937. (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1938. (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1939. (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1940. (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1943. (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1944. (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1945. (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1946. (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1947. (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1948. (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1949. (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1950. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1951. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1952. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1953. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1954. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1955. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1956. (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1957. (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1958. (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1959. (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1960. (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1961. (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1962. (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1963. (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1964. (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1965. (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1966. (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1967. (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1968. (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1969. (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1970. (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1971. (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1972. (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1973. (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1974. (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1977. (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1978. (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1979. (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1980. (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1981. (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1982. (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1983. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1983. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1984. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1984. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1985. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1986. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1989. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- United Thank Offering, 1976-1978. (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Ushering Schedule, 1972-1978. (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Venture in Mission, 1978-1981. (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Vestry Attendance Records, 1961-1978. (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Vestry Minutes, 1912-1915. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  The Vestry Minutes, 1912-1923 (Misc. reel 5857); 1935-1940 (Misc. reel 5858); 1950-1970 (Misc. reel 5859); 1971-1975 (Misc. reel 5860); 1976-1979 (Misc. reel 5861); 1980-1987 (Misc. reel 5862); and 1987-1988 (Misc. reel 5863) are also available on microfilm.
- Vestry Minutes, 1915-1919. (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Vestry Minutes, 1919-1920. (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Vestry Minutes, 1920-1921. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Vestry Minutes, 1921-1923. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Vestry Minute Book, 1922-1928. (Box 47)
- Vestry Minute Book, 1929-1934. (Box 48)
- Vestry Minutes, 1935. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Vestry Minutes, 1936. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Vestry Minutes, 1937. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Vestry Minutes, 1938. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Vestry Minutes, 1939. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Vestry Minutes, 1940. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Vestry Minutes, 1941. (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Vestry Minutes, 1942. (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Vestry Minutes, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Vestry Minutes, 1944. (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Vestry Minutes, 1945. (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Vestry Minutes, 1946. (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Vestry Minutes, 1947. (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Vestry Minutes, 1948. (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Vestry Minutes, 1949. (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Vestry Minutes, 1950. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Vestry Minutes, 1951. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Vestry Minutes, 1952. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Vestry Minutes, 1953. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Vestry Minutes, 1954. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Vestry Minutes, 1955. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Vestry Minutes, 1956. (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Vestry Minutes, 1957. (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Vestry Minutes, 1958. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Vestry Minutes, 1959. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Vestry Minutes, 1960. (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Vestry Minutes, 1961. (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Vestry Minutes, 1962. (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Vestry Minutes, 1963. (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Vestry Minutes, 1964. (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Vestry Minutes, 1965. (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Vestry Minutes, 1966. (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Vestry Minutes, 1967. (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Vestry Minutes, 1968. (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Vestry Minutes, 1969. (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Vestry Minutes, 1970. (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Vestry Minutes, 1971. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Vestry Minutes, 1972. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Vestry Minutes, 1973. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Vestry Minutes, 1974. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Vestry Minutes, 1974. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Vestry Minutes, 1975. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Vestry Minutes, 1976. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Vestry Minutes, 1977. (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Vestry Minutes, January-June 1978. (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Vestry Minutes, July-December 1978. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Vestry Minutes, 1979. (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Vestry Minutes, 1980. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Vestry Minutes, January-May 1981. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Vestry Minutes, June-December 1981. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Vestry Minutes, January-May 1982. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Vestry Minutes, June-December 1982. (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Vestry Minutes, 1983-1985. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Vestry Minutes, 1986. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Vestry Minutes, January-February 1987. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Vestry Minutes, March-April 1987. (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Vestry Minutes, May-June 1987. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Vestry Minutes, July-August 1987. (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Vestry Minutes, September-October 1987. (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Vestry Minutes, November-December 1987. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Vestry Minutes, January-February 1988. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Vestry Minutes, March-April 1988. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Vestry Minutes, May-June 1988. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Vestry Minutes, July-August 1988. (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Vestry Minutes, September-October 1988. (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Vestry Minutes, November-December 1988. (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Vestry -- Terms of Vestrymen, not dated. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Vestry Worship: Shreveport, Louisiana Choir 1980-1981. (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Visitors Register, 1956-1967. (Box 44)
- Visitors Register, 1967-1972. (Box 44)
- Visitors Register, 1973-1978. (Box 44)
- Virginia Branch of the Women's Auxiliary -- Year Book, 1958-1959. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Warnecke Dinner and Dedication, 1978. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Weddings, 1978-1979. (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Committee Chairs and Officers Annual Reports, 1950-1955. (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Committee Chairs and Officers Annual Reports, 1955-1956. (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Committee Chairs and Officers Annual Reports, 1958. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Correspondence, 1947-1956. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Financial Ledger, 1925-1948. (Box 43)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Financial Ledger, 1960-1971. (Box 49)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Goodwin Chapter Year Book, 1959. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Loose Scrap Book Items, 1928-1961. (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Loose Scrap Book Pages,.
- Women's Auxiliary Minute Book, 1897. (Box 43)
- Women's Auxiliary Minute Book, 1920-1924. (Box 46)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1936. (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1937. (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1938. (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1939. (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1940. (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1941. (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1943. (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1944. (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1945. (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1946. (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1947. (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1950. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1951. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1952. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1953. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1955. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1956. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Women's Auxiliary Minutes, 1957. (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Women's Auxiliary -- Miscellaneous, 1926-1960. (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Women's Auxiliary to the National Council, Annual Conference of the Virginia Branch Minutes, 1954. (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Women's Auxiliary to the National Council, Virginia Diocesan Branch Report, 1957-1968. (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Bazaar, 1976-1978. (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Bazaar, 1977. (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Bazaar, 1979. (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Budgets, 1973-1976. (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Women of St. Mark's, 1977-1981. (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Chapter IV Minutes, 1964-1969. (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Chapter IV Minutes, 1969-1975. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Cookbook, 1977. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Educational Program, 1977-1978. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Women of St. Mark's -- General, 1977-1978. (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Women of St. Mark's -- General, 1978-1979. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Goodwin Chapter, 1945-1976. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Hospitality Committee, 1971-1975. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Meetings Attended, 1974-1976. (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1960. (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1963. (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1964. (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1965-1966. (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1966-1967. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1967-1968. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1968-1969. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1968-1970. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1969-1970. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1970-1971. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1972-1974. (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1974-1976. (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1974-1977. (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Minutes, 1975-1977. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Miscellaneous, 1953-1969. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Disbursement and Income Ledger, 1972-1978. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1970-1971. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1971-1972. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1972-1973. (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1973-1974. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1974-1975. (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer Ledger, 1975-1976. (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1970-1971. (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1971-1972. (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer's Reports, 1972-1974. (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Treasurer's Reports, 1977-1978. (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1966-1967. (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1967-1968. (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1969-1970. (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1970-1971. (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1971-1972. (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1972-1973. (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1974-1975. (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1975-1976. (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1976-1977. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1977-1978. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1978-1979. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1979-1980. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1980-1981. (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1981-1982. (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1984-1985. (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1985-1986. (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1986-1987. (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Women of St. Mark's -- Yearbook, 1987-1988. (Box 38, Folder 11)
- World Council of Churches, 1978. (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Year Book -- St. Mark's Episcopal Church, Gastonia, North Carolina, 1953-1955. (Box 38, Folder 13)
- "Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow", not dated. (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Program, Festival of the Holy Eucharist for the Celebration of the 150th Anniversary of St. Mark's Episcopal Church, 24 April 2016. (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Remarks of Hon. Robert C. Bobby Scott in the House of Representatives on the 150th Anniversary of St. Mark's Episcopal Church (p. E547), 20 April 2016. (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Letter from the Richmond City Council to St. Mark's Episcopal Church, 9 May 2016, extending congratulation for 150th anniversary. (Box 38, Folder 17)